Angelica Victoria

Web Developer



Education

Front-End Developer Certification SheCodes

2023-2024

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.)

University of California, Irvine

2014-2016

Contact



(831)435-9707



angelica@avictoria.dev



Rancho Cucamonga, California

About Me

I have experience working with JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Al, React, and Python to deliver exceptional customer experiences. Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining client satisfaction.

Skills

- Front-End Development
- React.js
- Responsive Development
- JavaScript
- · Critical Thinking
- Creativity

Experience

Front-End Developer

Wild Byte

June 2024-Present

Developed UI (user interface) for 2 eCommerce websites using HTML, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and CSS. Utilized SEO (Search Engine Optimization) best practices and techniques to optimize results.

Community Navigator

Tri-City Mental Health

December 2023-Present

Help individuals, families and caregivers gain access to needed resources, including informal community supports and formal services. Community Navigators identify and verify current available services to ensure community members are quickly connected to the support they need.

Intensive Case Manager

2022-2024

Brilliant Corners

Developed and implemented individualized case management services plans that ensured housing stability, and identified short and long-term goals.

Behavior Therapist

Creative Solutions for Hope

2021-2022

Designed and modified individual behavioral plans to target client needs. Provided essential services to support client health, safety and welfare. Summarized individual client data and test results and maintained meticulous documentation.

References

Jenna Cavelle

HULU / Entertainment Executive & Producer Phone: (310)498-3534

Email: jennacavelle@mac.com

Brittany Sefa-Boakye

Pinnacle Treatment Centers / C.M.A

Phone: (909)521-4747

Email: mabrittany@aol.com